數不清的歲月
但我總算是回來了
How slowly those years passed
now I'm finally here at last
天知道，我有多想你
Oh heaven knows, I missed you
數不清的夜晚
想著要如何補償你
I spent so many nights
wondering how I'd make things right
才能夠，讓你原諒我
Oh can you please, forgive me
我曾不懂這名為
孤獨的痛
I never knew how bad it'd hurt
to be alone
一千年過去，
我終於可以回家，噢...
It took a thousand years,
but now I'm finally coming home, oh...
即使經歷了這麼多
命運仍讓我回來陪你
After all we've been through,
fate has brought me back to you
我們都會變得
越來越堅強
We'll be stronger than
we've ever been before
即使黑暗蠢蠢欲動
它卻再也沒法吞噬我
And though darkness may creep in,
it won't take over again
因為我再不會離開你了
'Cause I'll be with you forever more
我不敢相信是真的
我等到你的回歸了
I can't believe it's true
that I've made it back to you
少了你，我是多麼失落
Oh, I was lost without you
有了你我就滿足
分離絕沒有好處
So happy by your side,
we're better unified
就這樣，持續到永遠
No other way I'd want to
我曾不懂這名為
孤獨的痛
I never knew how bad it'd hurt
to be alone
一千年過去，
我終於可以回家，噢...
It took a thousand years,
but now I'm finally coming home, oh...
即使經歷了這麼多
命運仍讓我回來陪你
After all we've been through,
fate has brought me back to you
我們比以前都
還要更堅強
Now we're stronger than
we've ever been before
即使黑暗蠢蠢欲動
它卻再也沒法吞噬我
And though darkness may creep in,
it won't take over again
因為我再不會離開你了
'Cause I'll be with you forever more
讓你受傷，我很抱歉
I'm sorry that I hurt you
多少道歉
才能撫平被拋棄的痛
So sorry
that I left you alone
但我想讓你知道
我從今天起之後
But now I want you to be sure
that as we open this new door
會一直留在你身邊
直到永遠
I will be there by your side
forever more
即使經歷了這麼多
命運仍讓我回來陪你
After all we've been through,
fate has brought me back to you
我們比以前都
還要更堅強
Now we're stronger than
we've ever been before
即使黑暗蠢蠢欲動
它卻再也沒法吞噬我
And though darkness may creep in,
it won't take over again
因為我再不會離開你了
'Cause I'll be with you forever more
即使經歷了這麼多
命運仍讓我回來陪你
After all we've been through,
fate has brought me back to you
我們比以前都
還要更堅強
Now we're stronger than
we've ever been before
即使黑暗蠢蠢欲動
它卻再也沒法吞噬我
And though darkness may creep in,
it won't take over again
因為我再不會離開你了
'Cause I'll be with you forever more